Dism++开发过程中使用的一些开源类库授权






==============================================================================================================================

DirectUI - UI Library

Written by Bjarke Viksoe (bjarke@viksoe.dk)
Copyright (c) 2006-2007 Bjarke Viksoe.

This code may be used in compiled form in any way you desire. These
source files may be redistributed by any means PROVIDING it is 
not sold for profit without the authors written consent, and 
providing that this notice and the authors name is included. 

This file is provided "as is" with no expressed or implied warranty.
The author accepts no liability if it causes any damage to you or your
computer whatsoever. It's free, so don't hassle me about it.
Beware of bugs.



==============================================================================================================================

DuiLib Copyright

Copyright (c) 2010-2011, duilib develop team(https:github.com/duilib/duilib).All rights reserved.

    Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met.

    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    
    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.




==============================================================================================================================

Memory DLL loading code

The Initial Developer of the Original Code is Joachim Bauch.

Portions created by Joachim Bauch are Copyright (C) 2004-2015
Joachim Bauch. All Rights Reserved.



==============================================================================================================================

zlib

zlib.h -- interface of the 'zlib' general purpose compression library
 version 1.1.3, July 9th, 1998

 Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler

 This software is provided 'as-is', without any express or implied
 warranty.  In no event will the authors be held liable for any damages
 arising from the use of this software.

 Permission is granted to anyone to use this software for any purpose,
 including commercial applications, and to alter it and redistribute it
 freely, subject to the following restrictions:

 1. The origin of this software must not be misrepresented; you must not
    claim that you wrote the original software. If you use this software
    in a product, an acknowledgment in the product documentation would be
    appreciated but is not required.
 2. Altered source versions must be plainly marked as such, and must not be
    misrepresented as being the original software.
 3. This notice may not be removed or altered from any source distribution.

 Jean-loup Gailly        Mark Adler
 jloup@gzip.org          madler@alumni.caltech.edu


 The data format used by the zlib library is described by RFCs (Request for
 Comments) 1950 to 1952 in the files ftp:ds.internic.net/rfc/rfc1950.txt
 (zlib format), rfc1951.txt (deflate format) and rfc1952.txt (gzip format).


    The 'zlib' compression library provides in-memory compression and
 decompression functions, including integrity checks of the uncompressed
 data.  This version of the library supports only one compression method
 (deflation) but other algorithms will be added later and will have the same
 stream interface.

    Compression can be done in a single step if the buffers are large
 enough (for example if an input file is mmap'ed), or can be done by
 repeated calls of the compression function.  In the latter case, the
 application must provide more input and/or consume the output
 (providing more output space) before each call.

    The library also supports reading and writing files in gzip (.gz) format
 with an interface similar to that of stdio.

    The library does not install any signal handler. The decoder checks
 the consistency of the compressed data, so the library should never
 crash even in case of corrupted input.

for more info about .ZIP format, see ftp:ftp.cdrom.com/pub/infozip/doc/appnote-970311-iz.zip
  PkWare has also a specification at ftp:ftp.pkware.com/probdesc.zip


==============================================================================================================================

rapidxml

http://rapidxml.sourceforge.net/

RapidXml is an attempt to create the fastest XML parser possible, while retaining useability, portability and reasonable W3C compatibility. It is an in-situ parser written in modern C++, with parsing speed approaching that of strlen function executed on the same data. 

RapidXml has been around since 2006, and is being used by lots of people. HTC uses it in some of its mobile phones. 

If you are looking for a stable and fast parser, look no further. Integration with your project will be trivial, because entire library is contained in a single header file, and requires no building or configuration. 

Current version is RapidXml 1.13. Also available is its online Manual with a full and detailed reference. You may also like to check Boost.PropertyTree library, which presents a higher level interface, and uses RapidXml as its default XML parser. 

The author of RapidXml is Marcin Kalicinski. 


Copyright � 2006, 2009 Marcin Kalicinski (kalita at poczta dot onet dot pl)



=============================================================================================================================

MsIsoReader

微软的一个开源ISO库，为Dism++提供ISO读取支持。

